<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: foodfightshow | Food Fight]]></title>
  <link href="http://foodfightshow.org//blog/categories/foodfightshow/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://foodfightshow.org//"/>
  <updated>2013-01-10T12:58:53-05:00</updated>
  <id>http://foodfightshow.org//</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Bryan Berry - Nathen Harvey - Matt Ray]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Food Fight Show - Year Two]]></title>
    <link href="http://foodfightshow.org//2013/01/food-fight-show-year-two.html"/>
    <updated>2013-01-02T11:09:00-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://foodfightshow.org//2013/01/food-fight-show-year-two</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Show Date:  2 January 2013</p>

<p>This episode is a look back at the Food Fight Show in 2012 and a discussion
of the changes planned for 2013.  The episode was recorded as a Google+
Hangout and streamed live on YouTube.</p>

<p>You can now <a href="http://bit.ly/ffsmail">subscribe to the Food Fight Show email newsletter</a>.</p>

<ul>
<li><a href="http://foodfightshow.org/2013/01/food-fight-show-year-two.html#video">Video</a></li>
<li><a href="http://foodfightshow.org/2013/01/food-fight-show-year-two.html#panel">Panel</a></li>
<li><a href="http://foodfightshow.org/2013/01/food-fight-show-year-two.html#outline">Outline</a></li>
<li>Download

<ul>
<li><a href="http://traffic.libsyn.com/foodfight/Food-Fight-Show-35-A-Year-in-Review.mp3">Audio</a></li>
<li><a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=g58tMXfE3CY">Video Stream</a></li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>


<h2>Watch Now<a name="video"></a></h2>

<iframe width="560" height="315" src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/g58tMXfE3CY" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>




<!-- more -->


<h2>Panel<a name="panel"></a></h2>

<ul>
<li>Bryan Berry <a href="http://github.com/bryanwb">github</a>, <a href="http://twitter.com/bryanwb">twitter</a>, irc: bryanwb, blog: <a href="http://devopsanywhere.blogspot.com">devopsanywhere</a></li>
<li>Mike Fiedler <a href="http://github.com/miketheman">github</a>, <a href="http://twitter.com/mikefiedler">twitter</a></li>
<li>Nathen Harvey <a href="http://github.com/nathenharvey">github</a>, <a href="http://twitter.com/nathenharvey">twitter</a>, irc: nathenharvey, <a href="http://nathenharvey.com">blog</a></li>
</ul>


<h2>Outline<a name="outline"></a></h2>

<h3>Learning Chef</h3>

<p>Nathen has started a
<a href="http://nathenharvey.com/blog/2012/12/06/learning-chef-part-1/">blog series</a>
aimed at helping new people get up and running with Chef.  We discussed the
series a bit in the episode.</p>

<h3>Food Fight Show in 2012</h3>

<p>Thank you for your support of the podcast this year!  We released 57
episodes and have seen about 40,000 downloads.  That's about 700 downloads
for each episode.  We hosted 4 Google+ Hangouts which have about 900
views.  We've enjoyed the Hangouts so much that we decided to use a Google+
Hangout, instead of Skype, to facilitate our <a href="http://foodfightshow.org/2012/12/ops-school-and-training-sysadmins.html">last episode of the year</a>.
This episode was <a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zpbr8F2RGBs">streamed live to YouTube</a>
and released as an audio podacast.</p>

<h4>Top Episodes</h4>

<p>Want to relive some of the best episodes from 2012?  Here's a list of our
five favorite episodes in the order they were aired:</p>

<ol>
<li><a href="http://foodfightshow.org/2012/05/episode-11-etsy-examined-how-best-do.html">Episode 11: Etsy Examined, How the Best Do Their Business</a></li>
<li><a href="http://foodfightshow.org/2012/05/episode-14-live-post-mortem-with-david.html">Episode 14: Post-Mortems with David Zwieback, John Allspaw, and Mike Rembetsy</a></li>
<li><a href="http://foodfightshow.org/2012/06/episode-18-monitoringsucks-with-lusis.html">Episode 18: Monitoringsucks</a></li>
<li><a href="http://foodfightshow.org/2012/08/jamie-winsor-and-michael-ivey-skool-us-on-berkshelf.html">Episode 24: Jamie Winsor and Michael Ivey on Berkshelf</a></li>
<li><a href="http://foodfightshow.org/2012/08/chatops-at-github-with-jesse-newland.html">Episode 25: ChatOps at Github with Jesse Newland</a></li>
</ol>


<h3>Listener Survey</h3>

<p>We recently opened up a <a href="http://bit.ly/ffssurvey">listener poll</a> to gather
some feedback from you on how we can make the show even more awesome in
2013.</p>

<p>A quick summary of the <a href="https://s3.amazonaws.com/foodfightshow/Survey+Results.pdf">survey results is now available</a>.
Thanks to everyone who participated.</p>

<h3>Hopes and dreams for 2013</h3>

<ul>
<li>Orchestration for deploys and better orchestration in general</li>
<li>Opscode provides test-kitchen CI to cookbooks developed by the community - as a service, across at least debian + redhat, but bsd support would be awesome</li>
<li>Some consensus on cookbook workflow(s)</li>
<li>erChef is widely deployed, implemented, and battle-hardened</li>
<li>Regional 1 day mini conferences and at least one in Europe!</li>
<li>A quantum leap in the Chef training suite, docs.opscode.com is good but just a start</li>
</ul>


<h3>Changes for 2013</h3>

<p>As we look forward to 2013, there are a couple of things that we're going
to change:</p>

<ol>
<li>Whenever feasible, episodes will now be recorded via Google+ Hangout
with a live stream posted to YouTube.</li>
<li>We will try to keep length of the what's cookin' plus topic discussion
to about one hour. The Picks section is our time to be self-indulgent and
it may spill over one hour. You are welcome to hit the stop button at that
point and switch to something more substantive.</li>
<li>We will start a regular Food Fight Show newsletter which will include
the content from the What's Cookin' section and any other noteworthy
items.
You can <a href="http://bit.ly/ffsmail">subscribe to the newsletter now</a>.</li>
<li>Alternate episodes w/ interactive hangouts??</li>
<li>Bryan will make a conscious effort to interrupt the guests less</li>
<li>The Food Fight theme song is awesome but many of our hosts and
panelists are music lovers.  We'll start using different music between
What's Cookin' and the Interview and new music at the close of the
show.
We'll ask our guests for suggestions or pull a gem out of our hosts'
playlists.</li>
</ol>


<p>The <a href="https://s3.amazonaws.com/foodfightshow/Survey+Results.pdf">listener survey</a>
gave us some ideas about what sort of topics you'd like to see covered on
the show.  We'll work to line-up those topics and would really appreciate
your help in doing so.  Is there someone you really want to hear from?  A
topic you'd really like to see covered?  Please let us know!</p>

<h2>Thank You!</h2>

<p>We really appreciate all of the time you've put in listening to the show in
2012.  We hope to see you at <a href="http://chefconf.opscode.com">#ChefConf 2013</a>
and other conferences throughout the year.</p>

<p>Thanks to all of our AWESOME guests through out the year!</p>

<p>We'd also like to thank <a href="http://www.opscode.com">Opscode</a> for their
continued support of the show.  They cover our hosting and bandwidth costs
and allow their employees to participate on the show on a regular basis.</p>

<p>Keep it hot!<br/>
Bryan &amp; Nathen</p>

<h2>Download</h2>

<ul>
<li><a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=g58tMXfE3CY">Watch the YouTube video</a> of
the episode.</li>
<li><a href="http://traffic.libsyn.com/foodfight/Food-Fight-Show-35-A-Year-in-Review.mp3">Download the Audio file</a></li>
</ul>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
