<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: lapsu | Food Fight]]></title>
  <link href="http://foodfightshow.org//blog/categories/lapsu/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://foodfightshow.org//"/>
  <updated>2015-02-01T17:38:56+01:00</updated>
  <id>http://foodfightshow.org//</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Bryan Berry - Nathen Harvey - Matt Ray]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Surge Conf 2012]]></title>
    <link href="http://foodfightshow.org//2012/09/surge-conf-2012.html"/>
    <updated>2012-09-29T12:21:00+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://foodfightshow.org//2012/09/surge-conf-2012</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Nathen spent part of this week at <a href="http://omniti.com/surge/2012">Surge Conference</a> and was able to grab a bunch of the presenters for some quick interviews.  We also had a chance to sit down with <a href="http://twitter.com/novustiro">Michael Bevilacqua-Linn</a> earlier in the week to discuss his presentation.</p>

<p>Here's a list of links to all of the Surge-related episodes:</p>

<ul>
<li><a href="http://traffic.libsyn.com/foodfight/Food-Fight-Show-28-BigData.mp3">Episode 28:  Big Data in the Small: Why N Tier Architectures Are an Antipattern</a></li>
<li><a href="http://traffic.libsyn.com/foodfight/Food-Fight-Show-29-Surge-Ryan-Kennedy.mp3">Update from Surge with Ryan Kennedy from Yammer</a></li>
<li><a href="http://traffic.libsyn.com/foodfight/Surge-2-PagerDuty.mp3">Update from Surge with Andrew Miklas From PagerDuty</a></li>
<li><a href="http://traffic.libsyn.com/foodfight/Surge-3-Knewton.mp3">Update from Surge with Alejandro Companioni and Dave Zwieback from Knewton</a></li>
<li><a href="http://traffic.libsyn.com/foodfight/Surge-4-Appnexus-cleaned.mp3">Update from Surge with Mike Nolet from AppNexus</a></li>
<li><a href="http://traffic.libsyn.com/foodfight/Surge-5-Etsy.mp3">Update from Surge with Matt Grahamn from Etsy</a></li>
<li><a href="http://traffic.libsyn.com/foodfight/Food-Fight-Show-29-Kate-Mats.mp3">Episode 29:  Interview with Kate Matsudaira</a></li>
<li><a href="http://traffic.libsyn.com/foodfight/Surge-6-Theo.mp3">Wrap-up Surge with Theo Schlossnagle</a></li>
</ul>


<p>Email <a href="mailto:info@foodfightshow.org">info@foodfightshow.org</a> if you presented at Surge and would like to share your experience on the Food Fight Show.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Surge Update with Matt Grahamn from Etsy]]></title>
    <link href="http://foodfightshow.org//2012/09/surge-update-with-matt-grahamn-from-etsy.html"/>
    <updated>2012-09-29T11:58:00+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://foodfightshow.org//2012/09/surge-update-with-matt-grahamn-from-etsy</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Show Date:  Friday, 28 September 2012</p>

<p><a href="http://traffic.libsyn.com/foodfight/Surge-5-Etsy.mp3">Download the episode</a></p>

<p>In this DevOps Delicacy, Nathen sits down with <a href="http://twitter.com/lapsu">Matt Grahamn</a> from Etsy.  They discussed Matt's Surge presentation:</p>

<!-- more -->


<h4><a href="http://omniti.com/surge/2012/sessions/changing-etsys-architectural-foundation-with-continuous-deployment">Changing Etsy's Architectural Foundation with Continuous Deployment</a></h4>

<p>You hate that crusty old hunk of company technology that has long outlived the reasons it was adopted in the first place. But after all this time, it's stuck in the middle of everything; how to get rid of it?</p>

<p>At Etsy, we have successfully replaced our biggest problems with the small fixes of Continuous Deployment. How did deployment arrive at the state it is in today from the primitive practices of the 1980s? What practices and tools make it possible to deploy production code more than 50 times per day?</p>

<p>How does such frequent change actually improve quality and agility? Where can Continuous Deployment be applied? Finally, see how Continuous Deployment brings changes to an architectural foundation from a state of impossibility to the realm of safety and feasibility.</p>

<p>Surge - Interview with Matt Grahamn - <a href="http://traffic.libsyn.com/foodfight/Surge-5-Etsy.mp3">Download here</a></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
